<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mundane on Casual Grinder Flash Fictions</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/mundane/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mundane on Casual Grinder Flash Fictions</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 20:21:37 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/mundane/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Erudit Lust</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/erudit-lust/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 20:21:37 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/erudit-lust/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The sky was covered by white pigeons, and the streets were throbbing with busy vehicles. Lorence was excited about his new technical job. With a bright smile, he approached his colleagues, trying to fit in.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However, the work was fascinating, advanced technologies were introduced like a whirlwind and he, Lorence couldn’t help but feel overwhelmed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Yet he approached the task with curiosity and energy. His colleagues were willing to guide him whenever he needed help. He dove into learning, bit by bit, until he mastered his tools.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It Is Not Another Day</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/it-is-not-another-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2024 10:35:31 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/it-is-not-another-day/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Clair&amp;rsquo;s tummy growled with hunger; she had no time to cook. The plans were ready, and the lessons were about to begin. Yet time ticked away as if it were about to leave her behind.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;She ran through the sidewalks and hailed a public vehicle. Once seated, she calmed herself, as if this brief moment was hers alone. The vehicle sped quickly, and soon it was time to get off and walk toward a towering building.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After the Time Between Day and Night</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/after-the-time-between-day-and-night/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2024 18:40:24 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/after-the-time-between-day-and-night/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The road was inevitable as a bachelorette walked toward the building. Inside, a man in a dark suit waited for her, watching her through the glass walls. She passed through and greeted him with a smile honed by years of practice.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Good day, sir. May I ask how I can help you?&amp;rdquo; she said, her voice hints at worry.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The man sighed, his eyes stared at her unwavering. He replied, ”You&amp;rsquo;ve had a golden journey, but remember&amp;hellip;” He paused, the words heavy, “All roads lead to me.”&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
