<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Casual Grinder Flash Fictions</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Casual Grinder Flash Fictions</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 22:12:36 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Weeks of Seamless Eternity</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/weeks-of-seamless-eternity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 22:12:36 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/weeks-of-seamless-eternity/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;‘Why do I do this?’ He asked himself. Trembling thighs, lying on the floor—past nineteen in the evening.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“Seventy seven… seventy seven…” he chanted, that number never left his mind for two weeks. Things were… at least daunting for him—After all, he had set a three- to six-day commitment per week. But hey, he’s done it for three months already!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Weekdays were draining at work, but he chose to proceed in the sanctuary of strain instead of the leisure of home.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your Sailor&#39;s Vow</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/your-sailors-vow/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 12:34:56 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/your-sailors-vow/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;To the person I adore,&#xA;Who owns a vast ocean in her eyes.&#xA;Serene under a cloudless sky,&#xA;How I wished I had found it sooner.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I knew never was the ocean calm,&#xA;Nor does it reflect me in its raging waves.&#xA;I once traversed such turbulent waters,&#xA;Goodness! How frightening it was.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However, in stormy solitary night even,&#xA;I am set for a perpetual sail.&#xA;For unlike those days of turmoil,&#xA;For you, I vow to be brave.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beating Relic</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/beating-relic/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 10:03:53 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/beating-relic/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A relic that can imbue life to the colorless fabric of reality remains in a state of stasis. It has been years since it was. Unchanged. No cold and no warmth either.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Seasons crossed the scarlet barren land of no progress. Many had assumed themselves as catalysts and only met their doom. Yet one unremarkable soul had braved.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The great mage—renowned with years of deep understanding—who concealed the relic in perpetual stagnation laments that someone had barged in and put an end to the stasis.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duty Calls</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/duty-calls/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 22:54:25 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/duty-calls/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Lab speaks in silence, after that, noises can be heard. White walls are stained by dried red under the lined lights. Cut here and there, it is just another day against the captive specimen.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If duty calls, then I could engage in horror. I’ve done this. It was a great pursuit in biology. Well, It once was, before the day it striked.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Have nothing now but disgraced perhaps. Still, I’ll pluck one finger and another. One organ and another, and there will be far more worse.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clothe in Reverie</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/clothe-in-reverie/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 21:30:10 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/clothe-in-reverie/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Twisted and ticking, the doors hinged, creaked open, and gave passage through a dark room. The metallic click of the key grew silent as it found itself hung to the side. Dim light began to illuminate the room. Cracks of bones echoed as Ken twisted his neck—it sounded like twigs that snapped in two.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;He took a seat on the only visible chair in the area; his fingers, meanwhile, brushed for a lump in a flat panel. Ken leaned all his weight on the chair’s backrest; both hands hung low. His eyes drifted to the wall where a framed jersey was mounted—it almost touched the room&amp;rsquo;s ceiling.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My 2024 NaNoWriMo Entry</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/my-2024-nanowrimo-entry/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 13:06:31 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/my-2024-nanowrimo-entry/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi! I’ve decided to take on the 2024 NaNoWriMo challenge this November, and I&amp;rsquo;ll be sharing my progress here.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project Title:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.novlr.org/share/6729a9180eb2890021c2c039/6715f5ddfeec660022fb1223/671f64a2f1233d849b526513&#34;&gt;Calamity Seal&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note:&lt;/strong&gt; This is unedited, quick-draft writing using simple vocabulary to keep up with the pace—I&amp;rsquo;m aiming for about 100–250 words every 10 minutes with a minimum of 1100 words per day.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ll be updating soon, so stay tuned! I’m also considering whether I’d like to self-publish or seek a publisher to support the book once it’s complete.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Erudit Lust</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/erudit-lust/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 20:21:37 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/erudit-lust/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The sky was covered by white pigeons, and the streets were throbbing with busy vehicles. Lorence was excited about his new technical job. With a bright smile, he approached his colleagues, trying to fit in.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However, the work was fascinating&amp;mdash;advanced technologies were introduced like a whirlwind, and Lorence couldn’t help but feel overwhelmed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Yet he approached the task with curiosity and energy. His colleagues were willing to guide him whenever he needed help. He dove into learning, bit by bit, until he mastered his tools.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It Is Not Another Day</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/it-is-not-another-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2024 10:35:31 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/it-is-not-another-day/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Clair&amp;rsquo;s tummy growled with hunger; she had no time to cook. The plans were ready, and the lessons were about to begin. Yet time ticked away as if it were about to leave her behind.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;She ran through the sidewalks and hailed a public vehicle. Once seated, she calmed herself, as if this brief moment was hers alone. The vehicle sped quickly, and soon it was time to get off and walk toward a towering building.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After the Time Between Day and Night</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/after-the-time-between-day-and-night/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2024 18:40:24 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/after-the-time-between-day-and-night/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The road was inevitable as a bachelorette walked toward the building. Inside, a man in a dark suit waited for her, watching her through the glass walls. She passed through and greeted him with a smile honed by years of practice.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Good day, sir. May I ask how I can help you?&amp;rdquo; she said, her voice hints at worry.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The man sighed, his eyes stared at her unwavering. He replied, ”You&amp;rsquo;ve had a golden journey, but remember&amp;hellip;” He paused, the words heavy, “All roads lead to me.”&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
