<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Casual Grinder Novelettes</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Casual Grinder Novelettes</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 12:33:24 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cold Flame Sparks</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/cold-flame-sparks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 20:33:44 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/cold-flame-sparks/</guid>
      <description>Clanging clashes of weapons can be heard in the darkest part of the forest swamp. A muddy surface impeded anyones swift movement. The splatter of green and red blood fills the air with the scents of rust and spoiled salmon. As the moonlight filters through the dense canopy of the forest, A lady with hair that dances like flames emits a bluish colour that can take the attention of all beings including the forest swamp itself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lore of Alterhex</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/lore-of-alterhex/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 22:44:16 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/lore-of-alterhex/</guid>
      <description>In the primordial abyss of utter darkness, where only the vast realms of time and space existed, six divine dragons emerged—beings of unimaginable power and elemental influence. Among them were the Wind and Water Dragons, who, in their cosmic wanderings, discovered a massive boulder drifting alone in the void. The Water Dragon claimed the boulder, enveloping it entirely in a great ocean. This act ignited the fury of the Wind Dragon, who retaliated by gathering cosmic rocks from the void and hurling them into the ocean, causing waves and upheavals that shaped the land in a fierce display of power.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
