<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>World of Altehex on Casual Grinder Novellettes</title>
    <link>http://localhost:51075/categories/world-of-altehex/</link>
    <description>Recent content in World of Altehex on Casual Grinder Novellettes</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 22:44:16 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:51075/categories/world-of-altehex/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Lore of Alterhex</title>
      <link>http://localhost:51075/posts/lore-of-alterhex/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 22:44:16 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:51075/posts/lore-of-alterhex/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Cut out summary from your post content here.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fallen&#39;s Watcher</title>
      <link>http://localhost:51075/posts/fallens-watcher/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 13:38:34 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:51075/posts/fallens-watcher/</guid>
      <description>“You better not screw it up, my dear.” The maiden caressed her lioness pet while watching a deer from afar. It was a clear day on the plains of Yagacan, at a time when there was nothing to do but hunt.&#xA;Her furry companion snorted in disbelief and growled as if sighing. The last time the duo hunted, Lilac had cried because she pitied their prey. How could she not? The discord of the target felt so vivid to her that it was as if she were the one being hunted herself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whispering Wounds</title>
      <link>http://localhost:51075/posts/article-title/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 11:16:15 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:51075/posts/article-title/</guid>
      <description>The hiss of the grass had been going on for an hour now. Lilac was panting as she desperately clung to her prey for the day, moving with precise efficiency as she chased the wild, carnivorous buck. Not just any buck, but a huge gray one. Lilac was armed with a formidable arsenal of hunting weapons, yet they seemed ineffective against the wounded beast.&#xA;As the minutes passed, Lilac tripped and fell onto the grassy land of the Yagacan plains, a place where tall grass and scattered shrubs stood against the piercing sunlight.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
